One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Fight, crash through, and face the challenge!
These are our hard knock days.
Can't quench our thirst with a peaceful, everyday life.
Here we go - don't ever run away!
Let's go on living as the mighty winds take us!
We've still got so far to go.
Gotta keep going through the hard knock days.
Let's do it again, yes, baby. How many times
do I have to stand back up to make my dream come true?
Feels like the strength of my resolve
is put to the test everyday.
Hey, let's go!
I don't want to make excuses and settle for being mediocre.
We leapt into a crazy, lawless world.
As I struggled for a foothold, reality caught me off guard.
Even if it beats me, hits me, knocks me down again,
Oh!
Only when we get back on our feet and look forward,
will we have the last laugh, be the winners!
We gotta go down this glory road, till we reach our goal!
Fight, shake it off, act strong!
These are our hard knock days.
There's no such thing as a safe choice.
Here we go - we'll always be the strongest!
Let's keep moving - never mind the consequences.
Let's put our wishes all together,
and keep on going through the hard knock days.
The Curse of Heart
Has your sword ever broken?
Huh?
Yeah, it's happened a few times, I guess.
Including by you.
Were it clad in Haki,
that same sword would not have shattered.
The slightest nick to your blades is a shame to you.
Every sword can become a Black Blade.
Until you master it, drinking is forbidden.
Huh?!
No nicks.
Behind the Former
Royal Plateasu
Was anyone harmed?
No, sir. It's all thanks to you, Isshou-san.
Because you temporarily levitated those stones, there are no casualties.
Luckily, we already set up downtown as an evacuation zone.
Well done.
Port town Acacia
Did you see that?!
That giant statue was sliced completely in half!
Does that mean the top commander was done in?
Royal Plateau
Pica-sama's down!
He's that strong, and yet he didn't enter the competition?
What a humble guy.
That power, yet he's merely Garp's grandson's subordinate?
He's good!
We managed to protect King Riku in the end, so I'll let it go. But still...
The factory...!
The factory that rose from the ground exploded!
What's going on?!
Inside the
SMILE factory
One more time!
Yeah!
Heave-ho!
Blow the factory to bits for making us suffer!
We'll never be fooled or forced to work again!
Hey, hey! Pica has been defeated and the factory just exploded, Doffy.
But the defeated will be brought back. The factory will be restored.
Celebrate while you can!
We still have the Healing Fruit power user, Mansherry, on our side!
Rebecca-sama!
Robiland!
Are you alright?
The Fourth Level
Outside the Palace
The Sunflower Field
Commander! You're Commander Kyros, right?
Yup! I see you rescued the princess, Leo!
You look so gallant! A spitting image of the statue!
It's the other way around.
Oh, you're badly injured.
I'll heal you right away.
Actually, hold on.
You must be Princess Mansherry.
I heard a lot about your power,
but there must be some limit to it.
Don't use it on me.
But you're bleeding everywhere!
I'm fine. I'm still conscious.
More importantly, I'm glad that you're okay. It must have been tough.
If you're willing to use your power, there are people all over the country in need of it!
What? This is...
This is Dressrosa?
Leo and the others explained the situation to me,
but I didn't expect it to be this bad...
Still, it looks like they succeeded in destroying the factory.
The battle has come to a crucial point!
This country was entrapped by Doflamingo.
Whether we can return it to the hands of King Riku...
or fall once again and become a land of despair...
Our hope now rests with a certain band of pirates!
Pirates?
In the royal palace...
On the top floor...
Luffyland... Lawland...
Those two are our last resort.
Luffy... Traf-kun...
Lucy...
Beneath the Palace
Inside the Outer Wall Tower
I've just entered the rampart tower.
Looks like something bad's about to go down.
Sabo-kun, can't you get here? Where are you?
I'm helping trapped prisoners escape from the Colosseum.
You're too far away.
You can handle pretty much anything on your own, right?
If I thought I could handle this, I wouldn't be calling you! This might affect Luffy-kun!
I'll be right there!
Jeez!
Former Royal Plateau
Zoro! Do you need a hand?
I'm okay! Ain't a scratch on me!
Zoro, thank you! I thought I was done for!
Zoro-dono, very well done!
Pirate, thank you!
When I saw you cut that giant statue with your swords, I could hardly believe my eyes!
Hold it, you guys!
Hold off on the excitement until that suffocating cage disappears!
It's still there, which means the key man hasn't been defeated yet.
Royal Palace
First Floor
Stop, Bellamy!
Stop!
That bastard isn't worth risking your life for!
That's for me to decide!
Your body's in tatters already...
If you keep fighting, you really will die!
Even if I die, if I can take you down...
Doflamingo might at least remember me a little!
He said he set you free, but...
That's enough, Bellamy. I set you free.
Like you have always been.
...you didn't run, and now you're fighting me to the death...
He must have known you'd do this.
I'm sure he did! But so what?!
I respect him!
If I can at least die in a way that would impress him...
I'll be content!
Don't lie! This is the only option you have left, right?!
Because you're a man!
If you understand that much, shut up and fight!
But you'll die for nothing!
No, this is what I want.
If I'm to meet my end, it should be...
by another man that I admire!
Where are you going, Straw Hat?!
The sky!
What are you saying?! Bellamy has changed!
You've changed, Bellamy.
You're my friend!
Thank you, Straw Hat!
Straw Hat!
If you refuse to fight me...
I'll just...
kill you!
Why're you just standing there?!
Put 'em up, coward!
If you know how to throw a punch, that is!
Die!
So long, Straw Hat!
Thank you for calling me your friend!
I get it now!
That I admired the wrong man!
And how pathetic I am!
I know I'm an idiot...
but even an idiot has principles he must stick to!
Doflamingo!
The beast is roaring.
He should hurry on up here.
I'm sure he'll be surprised, Law...
When he sees your dead body.
A few minutes ago The Royal Palace
Sticky Launcher!
He's still alive.
Hey, hey, hey, Law.
Why don't you just accept defeat already?
You really should rest, Law.
You're not even a match for me on my own.
Why would you want to challenge both of us at the same time?
Straw Hat won't make it up here that easily.
If he had the guts to kill his "friend" right off the bat,
he might have been able to save you, but...
He's such a naive idiot!
Born in the hell that was White Town...
Spending your entire childhood with no hope whatsoever for your future...
But then you met my younger brother, Corazón.
He extended your life expectancy,
and you carried on resenting me, as if you were a ghost of him...
Living only for revenge, what an astounding obsession!
However...
it ends now.
What a waste of thirteen years.
I feel sorry for you.
Your death is inevitable.
You will die a completely meaningless death!
But, if you're going to die anyway...
Wouldn't you rather make something of it?
I have an idea we'd both benefit from.
I'm only going to say this once, so listen carefully,
Trafalgar D. Water Law.
Perform the ultimate Operation Fruit technique on me... the Eternal Youth Operation... and die.
In exchange, I'll grant your wish, whatever it is.
Whatever it is?
If you really mean it...
it's a brilliant idea. We'd both benefit from it.
Alright, I'm in!
You're a very understanding man! Doffy will finally have eternal life!
Then...
Bring Cora-san back to life, right now!
When you're finished doing that,
go lick the asses of everyone in the country!
"No match for" you?
"No use pinning my hopes"?
Don't make me laugh!
You're the one not seeing the whole picture, Doflamingo!
The Straw Hats have caused all sorts of miracles in the past.
You can't beat Straw Hatter!
You won't be able to reclaim Caesar from him, either!
Law, how dare you say that to Doffy!
It's your future that's hanging by a thread-
The letters on your back, "Corazón"?
Are you trying to mock me?
And then there's the name of your crew, the "Heart Pirates"!
Are you trying to mock me?!
You won't even sit on the Seat of Hearts!
So why do you bear the Heart crest?!
Law!
So irritating!
Law, Corazón... This is it.
There's no one left to carry on your ridiculous tenacity!
The curse you've cast on me is broken!
Present time Former Royal Plateau
Straw Hat just took down Bellamy.
That leaves two major enemies in the Donquixote Family.
The only ones left are
the top commander and chief of staff, Trebol,
and the Family boss, Donquixote Doflamingo!
It can't be!
What's the matter, Viola-sama?
Viola?
Our ranks have shrunk as well!
"Our ranks"? You mean out of us was taken out?
Trafalgar Law!
Your majesty?
In a situation where we can't let our guard down at any time,
it's all the more important to keep our people out of harm's way.
Yes, Sir! Let's go!
M-Me, too!
I'll go with you, too!
Me, too!
Alright! Let's go down to the city right now!
It's not too late to minimize casualties!
Yeah! Even though we can't fight, there are still things we can do!
Yeah! Let's go!
Then, all that's left is...
To put an end...
to everything.
Doflamingo!
You're late, Straw Hat.
Now that I've emancipated him,
Bellamy has become "free", right?
Don't play dumb! You knew full well...
that he wasn't gonna run away!
Rubber...
Elephant Gun!
Spiderweb!
I see. So Bellamy didn't run away.
What's so funny?!
Rubber...
Hawk Gatling!
Break White!
That's dangerous!
Hey, Traf!
Why're you bleeding so much?
What happened to your arm?
Hey!
Stay with me, Traf! Hey!
Traf!
He's dead. Obviously.
That's not true!
It is.
He seemed to have a great deal of faith in you, too.
He said you can work miracles.
Can you, Straw Hat?
I didn't think you were that strong
when I fought you, though...
Now, bring it on! There's only two of us left.
How dare you bastards!
Wait! Stay where you are!
No way...
The wall of strings...
is shrinking!
I'll have you follow Law in death shortly.
Let's end this game, shall we?
Mingo!
Wait.
Listen carefully, Straw Hatter.
Look!
It really is moving.
The string wall's moving!
Run for it!
Not even the outskirts of town are safe!
Hurry up and make a break for it!
Get to downtown!
It's the same in the west!
Reporting in! Eastern district, Carta!
Per other reports, the bird cage appears to be shrinking!
The islanders are all headed toward downtown!
The Royal Palace
Sooner or later...
everyone dies, correct?
Straw Hat, haven't you noticed?
The rules of the game have changed.
Game? What are you on about now?!
Just listen.
The bird cage that surrounds this town is shrinking, bit by bit.
It's like an umbrella, slowly closing.
It'll shred apart everything in this country.
In about...
an hour, give or take.
There's nowhere to run.
Save the people on the outskirts of the country, on the double!
Aye!
The weaker citizens have been evacuated
to the edges of the city, so hurry and get them!
Run to the center part of town!
Run! Here come the strings!
Hey! Somebody, help me!
Just freeing my legs would work!
Untie me! I don't wanna die!
T-T-The bird cage is shrinking?!
Former Royal Grounds
What's going on?! The bird cage... The bird cage...
Is this truly happening?
My word...
What do we do?! What can we do?!
Hey, Zoro!
The cage is heading toward us! What's gonna happen to us?!
We finally busted out from behind bars, only to be put behind them again?
Where are we supposed to run?!
How can he stoop so low?
Are you not yet satisfied, Doflamingo?
If the cage keeps shrinking like this...
That's it for Dressrosa!
The Royal Palace Grounds - Second Level
What's all that smoke and rumbling?
What in the world's going on?!
Luffy, hurry up! Kick Doflamingo's ass already!
You're our last hope!
That is right! Indeed! Certainly!
But that is too much to ask. The lives of everyone are in Luffy-dono's hands.
We are counting on you, Luffy-dono!
I am counting on you, too!
I'm not planning on sparing anyone.
What advantage would I gain in allowing people
that have learned this country's secrets survive?
Towns, people, animals...
Even your allies...
And you! Everyone dies!
In other words, your friends just died
a little earlier than they otherwise would have.
Right, Straw Hatter?
Isn't that what he used to call you?
Oh, you needn't worry.
I'll build another country.
Mingo, all I have to do to fix this
is kick your ass!
I've been trying to tell you, you can't do that.
You never learn!
Bullet String!
Rubber...
Join Law in death!
Chambres!
Law!
You're the one that's going to perish, Doflamingo!
Do it!
This operation will destroy you from the inside out!
Gamma Knife!
Doffy!
Law! How are you still alive?!
How are you using your Operation abilities without creating a Room?!
No, this is a Room!
It's at the cost of some of my lifespan,
but I created a Room so big you can't even see it!
What?!
I did it all for this moment... to set up this attack!
He missed my vital organs!
Chambres!
Mingo!
Wait.
I'm alive.
Listen carefully, Straw Hatter.
Don't turn around. I have a plan.
Nobody can defend against an attack from inside their body!
Even you can't counteract this technique!
Doffy, you're a king! Don't prostrate yourself!
Now you've really done it!
It's no use!
Even if you kill me, it's too late for you!
I won't let you live...
Law!
Rubber...
Jet Stamp!
Doffy!
Doffy! Are you alright?
You bastard!
Wait, Straw Hatter!
Traf...
That bastard... is mine!
Room!
You're finished, Doflamingo!
Law!
Damn you! What have you done to Doffy?!
Don't get in his way!
You just...
gathered people that were convenient to you
and called it a "family".
And when your real brother, Cora-san, tried to end your rampage, you...
He's free!
Yeah, that was a shame...
He betrayed me... even pointed a gun at me...
But you knew!
You knew Cora-san couldn't pull the trigger!
I would have pulled it.
I bet you would have.
You're the same as me.
I wanna destroy everything before my eyes!
Towns, houses, people... I wanna destroy them all!
Yeah... That's fine by me.
But on that day...
You should have died, not him!
Law, I'm sure you'll love to hear this...
Corazón was a drag and an eyesore to me.
He acquired this silly sense of justice
and wore that worthless heart of his on his sleeve.
He was an incompetent man.
When I killed him that day,
it was a huge load off my-
Counter Shock!
Go to hell you demonic bastard!
Doffy!
As expected of our king!
H-How the hell...
Given enough time, I can mend myself.
As we speak, the strings within my body are repairing my internal organs.
What?!
It's all about how you use your ability.
It's a bit different from recovery, though.
Good job on the suicide attack.
Sticky Chain!
Stop!
Sticky Stick!
I'll put you out of your misery. It's the least I can do.
Dammit!
Dammit...